[{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678855495,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":13357,"timeElapsed":68455},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678869086,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":13590,"timeElapsed":82047},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678873343,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":4255,"timeElapsed":86304},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678878706,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5362,"timeElapsed":91667},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678884757,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":6051,"timeElapsed":97718},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678893969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":9211,"timeElapsed":106930},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678905537,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":11567,"timeElapsed":118498},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678918217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":12679,"timeElapsed":131178},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678929192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":10975,"timeElapsed":142153},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678947576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":15558,"timeElapsed":160537},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678954528,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":6951,"timeElapsed":167488},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678958203,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3675,"timeElapsed":171164},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678962755,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":4551,"timeElapsed":175716},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678968695,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":5938,"timeElapsed":181656},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678979715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":11019,"timeElapsed":192676},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678983987,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":4271,"timeElapsed":196948},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678992631,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":8643,"timeElapsed":205592},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678995202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":2571,"timeElapsed":208163},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679029745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":32766,"timeElapsed":242706},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679034281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":4535,"timeElapsed":247242},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679037993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":3711,"timeElapsed":250954},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679042945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":4951,"timeElapsed":255906},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679046305,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3359,"timeElapsed":259266},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679051449,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":5143,"timeElapsed":264410},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679053757,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2307,"timeElapsed":266718},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679057721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3963,"timeElapsed":270682},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679060377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2655,"timeElapsed":273338},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679070816,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":8639,"timeElapsed":283777},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679073472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2655,"timeElapsed":286433},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679078304,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4831,"timeElapsed":291265},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679081864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3559,"timeElapsed":294825},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679084960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3095,"timeElapsed":297921},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679090040,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5079,"timeElapsed":303001},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679092084,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2043,"timeElapsed":305045},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679099324,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":7239,"timeElapsed":312285},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679103303,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3979,"timeElapsed":316264},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679114335,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":9347,"timeElapsed":327296},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679116659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2323,"timeElapsed":329620},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679125015,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8355,"timeElapsed":337976},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679129091,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4075,"timeElapsed":342052},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679132151,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":3059,"timeElapsed":345111},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679136646,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":4495,"timeElapsed":349607},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679140563,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":3915,"timeElapsed":353524},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679143566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":3003,"timeElapsed":356527},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679146478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2911,"timeElapsed":359439},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679149670,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":3191,"timeElapsed":362631},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679164422,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":13011,"timeElapsed":377383},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679166722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2299,"timeElapsed":379683},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679170690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3967,"timeElapsed":383651},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679174193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3503,"timeElapsed":387154},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679178605,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4411,"timeElapsed":391566},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679182581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":3975,"timeElapsed":395542},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679185265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2683,"timeElapsed":398226},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679187721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2455,"timeElapsed":400682},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679191217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":3495,"timeElapsed":404178},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679202373,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":9603,"timeElapsed":415334},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679206329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3955,"timeElapsed":419290},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679211432,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5103,"timeElapsed":424393},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679217672,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6239,"timeElapsed":430633},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679221008,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3335,"timeElapsed":433969},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679226072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5063,"timeElapsed":439033},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679230960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":4887,"timeElapsed":443921},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679233448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2487,"timeElapsed":446409},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679238036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":4587,"timeElapsed":450997},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679241828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":3791,"timeElapsed":454789},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679250799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":7507,"timeElapsed":463760},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679254331,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3531,"timeElapsed":467292},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679260451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":6119,"timeElapsed":473412},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679263487,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3035,"timeElapsed":476448},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679269023,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":5535,"timeElapsed":481984},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679274831,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5807,"timeElapsed":487792},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679277835,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3003,"timeElapsed":490796},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679284014,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":6178,"timeElapsed":496975},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679286602,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2587,"timeElapsed":499563},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679295874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":7495,"timeElapsed":508835},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679298830,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2955,"timeElapsed":511791},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679302678,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3847,"timeElapsed":515639},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679305810,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3131,"timeElapsed":518771},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679309586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3775,"timeElapsed":522547},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679314294,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":4707,"timeElapsed":527255},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679316445,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2151,"timeElapsed":529406},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679321949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":5503,"timeElapsed":534910},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679324921,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2971,"timeElapsed":537882},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679336825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":10343,"timeElapsed":549786},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679340477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":3651,"timeElapsed":553438},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679346245,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5767,"timeElapsed":559206},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679349237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2991,"timeElapsed":562198},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679352501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":3263,"timeElapsed":565462},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679356172,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":3671,"timeElapsed":569133},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679358444,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2271,"timeElapsed":571405},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679361716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3271,"timeElapsed":574677},{"subjectID":"jwb7yo3vnw","prolificID":"57dc590ddcda780001a0e157","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3eb5b14e7a0561f7d3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679364656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2939,"timeElapsed":577617}]